Herz, John H.; Papers ger015
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Political pamphlets, 9; 253 file folders
  - Marion H. McVitty.A Comparison and Evaluation of Current Disarmament Proposals as of March 1, 1964 (Box 20 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 95)
  - Horst Mendershausen.The Diplomat as a National and Transnational Agent: A Problem in Multiple Loyalty, 1973 (Box 20 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 96)
  - Richard L. and Anna J. Merritt.West Germany enters the seventies, 1971 April (Box 20 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 97)
  - Walter Millis.A World Without War, 1961 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 1)
  - Walter Millis.Permanent Peace, 1961 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 2)
  - Walter Millis.War and Revolution Today, 1965 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 3)
  - Albert Memmi.Who Is an Arab Jew?, 1975 February (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 4)
  - Clement Harry Moore.Tunisia After Bourguiba: Liberalization or Political Degeneration?, 1966 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 5)
  - S. Morisse.CYPRUS should welcome the U.N, 1965 February (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 6)
  - Edward L. Morse.Defense Autonomy in Gaullist France: Welfare Versus Warfare and the Dilemma of Insufficient Resources, 1972 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 7)
  - Philip E. Mosely.Russia After Stalin, 1955 May-1955 June (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 8)
  - David P. Mozingo.The United States in Asia: Evolution and Containment. 2nd printing, 1967 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 9)
  - Willard A. Mullins.On the Concept of Ideology in Political Science, 1973 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 10)
  - National Citizens' Commission on International Cooperation.Report of the Committee on Arms Control and Disarmament, 1965 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 11)
  - NATO Information Service.Harmel Report. Report on the Future Tasks of the Alliance, 1968 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 12)
  - Eric Norden.American Atrocities in Vietnam, 1966 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 13)
  - Office of the U.S. High Commissioner for Germany.Soviet Zone Constitution and Electoral Law, 1951 February 01 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 14)
  - Organisationsstatut. Schiedsordnung der Sozialdemokratischen Partei Deutschlands, 1970 May 14 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 15)
  - Robert E. Osgood.The Case for the MLF: A Critical Evaluation, Undated (1962?) (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 16)
  - Arnold Petersen.The Freeman's Vote, 1940 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 17)
  - Albert Pfitzer.The German Bundesrat, 1962 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 18)
  - Paul A. Porter.The Gulf of Aqaba: An International Waterway, 1957 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 19)
  - Pitman B. Potter.Article XIX of the Covenant of the League of Nations, 1941 August (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 20)
  - Press and Information Office, Federal Republic of Germany.Facts and Figures. A Comparative Survey of the Federal Republic of Germany and the German Democratic Republic, 1981 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 21)
  - Presse- und Informationsamtes der Bundesregierung.Die Regierung Adenauer, das fünfte Kabinett, 1963 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 22)
  - Robert Presthus.The Organizational Society. An Analysis and a Theory, 1962 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 23)
  - Paul Ramsey.The Limits of Nuclear War, 1963 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 24)
  - Harry Howe Ransom.Strategic Intelligence, 1973 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 25)
  - William E. Rappard.Albert Gallatin, Citoyen de Genève, Ministre des États-Unis, 1917 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 26)
  - Hans Reichel / Franz Ringer.Freedom of Association and the Relationship between the Two Sides of Industry, 1965 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 27)
  - Hans Reichel / Ottfried Wlotzke.Collective Bargaining and the Law Governing Collective Agreements, 1963 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 28)
  - Henry Reiff.Transition from League of Nations to United Nations, 1946 May (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 29)
  - Report of the Committee on the Economic Impact of Defense and Disarmament, 1965 July (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 30)
  - Research Center for Peace and Unification, Seoul, Korea.Socio-Cultural Comparison between South and North Korea, 1975 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 31)
  - Revelle, Roger.Man and the Sea in the 21st Century, 1968 June (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 32)
  - Riezler, Kurt.Political Decisions in Modern Society, 1954 January (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 33)
  - Fred W. Riggs.Prismatic Society Revisited, 1973 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 34)
  - Alfonso García Robles.The Latin American Nuclear-Weapon-Free Zone, 1979 May (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 35)
  - Wilhelm Röpke.South Africa. An Attempt at a Positive Appraisal, 1964 May (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 36)
  - James N. Rosenau.The Adaptation of National Societies: A Theory of Political System Behavior and Transformation, 1970 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 37)
  - Zenon Rossides.The Problem of Cyprus, 1957 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 38)
  - Robert L. Rothstein.Alignment, Nonalignment, and Small Powers: 1945-1965, Undated (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 39)
  - Joachim Rottmann.Der Viermächte-Status Berlins, 1959 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 40)
  - Jose Maria Ruda.The Final Acceptance of International Conventions, 1976 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 41)
  - Heinz Sahmer.The Labour Courts, 1963 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 42)
  - Walter Scheel.Die Freien Demokraten, 1970 January (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 43)
  - Günther Schelp.The Contract of Service, 1965 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 44)
  - Dietrich Schindler.Die Verbindlichkeit der Beschlüsse des Völkerbundes, 1927 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 45)
  - Gerhard Schröder.Fester Kurs in bewegter Welt, 1966 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 46)
  - Gebhard Schweigler.German Foreign Policy, 1975 February (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 47)
  - Herbert Scoville Jr. / Kosta Tsipis.Can Space Remain A Peaceful Environment?, 1978 July (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 48)
  - The SED. Construction - Character - Situation, 1954 January (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 49)
  - Charles Seymour.Woodrow Wilson in Perspective, 1956 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 50)
  - Roberta S. Sigel.Race and Religion as Factors in the Kennedy Victory in Detroit, 1960, 1962 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 51)
  - I. Robert Sinai.Modernization and the Middle East, 1970 Spring (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 52)
  - J. David Singer.A General Systems Taxonomy for Political Science, 1971 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 53)
  - J. David Singer.Escalation and Control in International Conflict: A Simple Feedback Model, 1970 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 54)
  - J. David Singer.The Scientific Study of Politics: An Approach to Foreign Policy Analysis, 1972 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 55)
  - Social Democratic Party of Germany.Basic Programme of the Social Democratic Party of Germany, 1959 November 13-1959 November 15 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 56)
  - Social Democratic Party of Germany.SPD Party Conference 1966. The State of the Nation (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 57)
  - Society for Christian and Jewish Cooperation.Agreement between the Federal Republic of Germany and the State of Israel, 1962 September (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 58)
  - Sozialdemokratische Partei Deutschlands.Kundgebungen und Entschließungen des SPD-Parteitages in Dortmund vom 1. bis 5. Juni 1966 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 59)
  - The Stanley Foundation.Second Conference on the United Nations of 1975, 1967 July (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 60)
  - The Stanley Foundation.Conference on Energy and Nuclear Security in Latin America, 1978 April (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 61)
  - The Stanley Foundation.Comprehensive Programme of Disarmament, 1979 May (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 62)
  - The Stanley Foundation.The United Nations and Multilateral Sanctions: New Options for US Polilcy?, 1992 October 22-1992 October 24 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 63)
  - The Stanley Foundation.Political Symbol or Policy Tool? Making Sanctions Work, 1993 February 19-1993 February 21 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 64)
  - The Stanley Foundation.The UN Role in Intervention: Where Do We Go From Here?, 1993 June 13-1993 June 18 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 65)
  - The Stanley Foundation.State of the United Nations: Decline or Regeneration in the Next Fifty Years, 1994 June 19-1994 June 24 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 66)
  - The Stanley Foundation.Human Rights and US Foreign Policy: Who Controls the Agenda?, 1994 October 27-1994 October 29 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 67)
  - The Stanley Foundation.United Nations - Bretton Woods Collaboration: How Much Is Enough?, 1995 February 24-1995 February 26 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 68)
  - The Stanley Foundation.Shaping American Foreign Relations: The Critical Role of the Southwest, 1995 May 04-1995 May 06 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 69)
  - The Stanley Foundation.Making Peace With the Future: The United Nations and World Security, 1995 June 11-1995 June 16 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 70)
  - The Stanley Foundation.The United States and Cuba. Where Do We Go From Here?, 1995 October 26-1995 October 28 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 71)
  - The Stanley Foundation.American Relations With China and India: The Growing Impact of Politics and Society on Foreign Policy, 1995 October 26-1995 October 28 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 72)
  - The Stanley Foundation.The Role of the United Nations in Eliminating Weapons of Mass Destruction, 1996 February 23-1996 February 25 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 73)
  - The Stanley Foundation.The United Nations and the Twenty-First Century: The Imperative for Change, 1996 June 16-1996 June 21 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 74)
  - The Stanley Foundation.The Impact of Globalization: Shaping the Greater Twin Cities Response, 1963 September 06-1963 September 07 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 75)
  - The Stanley Foundation.The Persian Gulf: Challenges for a New Administration, 1996 October 24-1996 October 26 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 76)
  - The Stanley Foundation.Weapons of Mass Destruction: Are the Nonproliferation Regimes Falling Behind?, 1996 October 24-1996 October 26 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 77)
  - The Stanley Foundation.Rebuilding Russia: The Next Phase, 1996 October 24-1996 October 26 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 78)
  - The Stanley Foundation.Post-Conflict Justice: The Role of the International Community, 1997 April 04-1997 April 06 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 79)
  - Statement by Adenauer's Fourth Government Given to the German Bundestag on November 29, 1961 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 80)
  - Erich Strättling.Wie entsteht ein Bundesgesetz?, 1952 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 81)
  - Leon Trotsky.Europe and America: Two Speeches on Imperialism, 1971 March (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 82)
  - L. Trotzki.Der einzige Weg, 1932 September (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 83)
  - L. Trotzki.Sowjetwirtschaft in Gefahr (vor dem zweiten Fünfjahresplan), 1932 November (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 84)
  - Unitarian Commission on World Order.Toward Mutual Understanding. The Story of UNESCO, 1947 September (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 85)
  - United Nations Association of the United States of America.China, the United Nations and United States Policy, 1967 September (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 86)
  - United Nations, Dept. of Social Affairs.The Impact of the Universal Declaration of Human Rights, 1953 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 87)
  - Richard W. Van Wagenen.Research in the International Organization Field, 1952 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 88)
  - Verband deutscher Soldaten.Sonderdruck des Soldatenurteils, 1953 July 04 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 89)
  - Harold M. Vinacke.United States Policy Toward China, 1961 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 90)
  - Vorstand der Sozialdemokratischen Partei Deutschlands.Grundsatzprogramm der Sozialdemokratischen Partei Deutschlands, 1959 November (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 91)
  - Lawrence D. Weiler.The Arms Race, Secret Negotiations and the Congress, 1976 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 92)
  - Walter A. Weisskopf et al.Looking Forward: The Abundant Society, 1966 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 93)
  - Karl Welzel.The Protection of Working Mothers, 1963 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 94)
  - Norman Wengert.The Ideological Basis of Conservation and Natural-Resources Policies and Programs, 1962 November (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 95)
  - Harvey Wheeler.The Restoration of Politics, 1965 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 96)
  - Heinrich Windelen.Basic Aspects of German reunification, 1984 February 07 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 97)
  - Francis D. Wormuth.The Vietnam War: The President versus the Constitution, 1968 April (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 98)
  - Gordon Zahn.An Alternative to War, 1963 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 99)
  - Abdul Aziz Zuabi.Options Open for Israel-Arab Cooperation, 1971 December 27 (Box 21 (9-Political pamphlets), Folder 100)
- Research materials, 1944-1994; 10; 187 file folders
  This series is comprised almost exclusively of newspaper clippings collected by Herz over a 50-year period on topics of interest and used as reference materials for his writings, lectures and courses taught.
  Arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - African States (excluding South Africa, Egypt), 1949-1994; Clippings (Box 22 (10-Research materials), Folder 1)
  - Albania, 1944-1993; Clippings (Box 22 (10-Research materials), Folder 2)
  - American Foreign Policy Newsletter (founded by Hans J. Morgenthau), 1979-1986 (Box 22 (10-Research materials), Folder 3)
  - American Foreign Policy Newsletter, 1987-1994 (Box 22 (10-Research materials), Folder 4)
  - Amnesty International. Newsletters, 1977-1989 (Box 22 (10-Research materials), Folder 5)
  - Arab Countries (including Egypt), 1945-1980; Clippings (Box 22 (10-Research materials), Folder 6)
  - Argentina, 1946-1994; Clippings (Box 22 (10-Research materials), Folder 7)
  - Arms Control, Disarmament, 1949-1975; Clippings (Box 22 (10-Research materials), Folder 8)
  - Arms Control, Disarmament, 1976-1981; Clippings (Box 22 (10-Research materials), Folder 9)
  - Armaments, Arms Control, 1980-1985; Clippings (Box 22 (10-Research materials), Folder 10)
  - Armaments, Arms Control, 1986-1990; Clippings (Box 22 (10-Research materials), Folder 11)
  - Armaments, Arms Control, 1991-1994; Clippings (Box 22 (10-Research materials), Folder 12)
  - Australia, New Zealand, 1949-1993; Clippings (Box 22 (10-Research materials), Folder 13)
  - Austria, 1945-1993; Clippings (Box 22 (10-Research materials), Folder 14)
  - Baltic States, 1991-1994; Clippings (Box 23 (10-Research materials), Folder 1)
  - Belgium, Holland, 1948-1993; Clippings (Box 23 (10-Research materials), Folder 2)
  - Brazil, 1940-1993; Clippings (Box 23 (10-Research materials), Folder 3)
  - Bulgaria, 1947-1993; Clippings (Box 23 (10-Research materials), Folder 4)
  - Canada, 1949-1993; Clippings (Box 23 (10-Research materials), Folder 5)
  - Cartoons, 1938-1960; Clippings (Box 23 (10-Research materials), Folder 6)
  - China, Tibet, Taiwan, Hong Kong, 1945-1994; Clippings (Box 23 (10-Research materials), Folder 7)
  - Churches in International Relations, 1942-1994; Clippings (Box 23 (10-Research materials), Folder 8)
  - Civil Rights and Liberties, 1949-1975; Clippings (Box 23 (10-Research materials), Folder 9)
  - Cold War, 1949-1994; Clippings (Box 23 (10-Research materials), Folder 10)
  - Constitutions of countries, Undated (Box 23 (10-Research materials), Folder 11)
  - Crime and Punishment, War Crimes, 1989; Clippings (Box 23 (10-Research materials), Folder 12)
  - Czechoslovakia (Czech Republic, Slovakia), 1948-1994; Clippings (Box 23 (10-Research materials), Folder 13)
  - Democratic Succession, 1978-1981; Clippings (Box 23 (10-Research materials), Folder 14)
  - Demographic Problems, World Population, 1948-1994; Clippings (Box 23 (10-Research materials), Folder 15)
  - Democracy, 1978-1979; Clippings (Box 23 (10-Research materials), Folder 16)
  - Dictatorship to Democracy, 1946-1982; Clippings (Box 23 (10-Research materials), Folder 17)
  - Diplomatic History, Documents, 1939-1991; Clippings (Box 23 (10-Research materials), Folder 18)
  - Education, Press, Undated; Clippings (Box 23 (10-Research materials), Folder 19)
  - Energy, 1973-1974; Clippings (Box 23 (10-Research materials), Folder 20)
  - Environmental Problems, 1971-1994; Clippings (Box 23 (10-Research materials), Folder 21)
  - European Community (EC), European Union (EU), 1947-1994; Clippings (Box 24 (10-Research materials), Folder 1)
  - European Left, 1970-1977; Clippings (Box 24 (10-Research materials), Folder 2)
  - Federalism, Local & State Government, 1953-1994; Clippings (Box 24 (10-Research materials), Folder 3)
  - Foreign Aid, Third World Countries, 1949-1994; Clippings (Box 24 (10-Research materials), Folder 4)
  - France: Colonies (excluding Indochina), 1952-1994; Clippings (Box 24 (10-Research materials), Folder 5)
  - France: Domestic issues, 1941-1994; Clippings (Box 24 (10-Research materials), Folder 6)
  - France: Foreign relations, 1946-1994; Clippings (Box 24 (10-Research materials), Folder 7)
  - Futurology, 1978-1979; Clippings (Box 24 (10-Research materials), Folder 8)
  - Germany: Civil Service, Federalism, 1953-1992; Clippings (Box 24 (10-Research materials), Folder 9)
  - Germany: DDR, 1971-1989; Clippings (Box 24 (10-Research materials), Folder 10)
  - Germany: DDR, 1990-1994; Clippings (Box 24 (10-Research materials), Folder 11)
  - Germany: Demography, Economy, Labor, 1969-1994; Clippings (Box 24 (10-Research materials), Folder 12)
  - Germany: Denazification, 1949-1982; Clippings (Box 24 (10-Research materials), Folder 13)
  - Germany: Elections, 1953-1991; Clippings (Box 24 (10-Research materials), Folder 14)
  - Germany: Executive, 1965-1994; Clippings (Box 24 (10-Research materials), Folder 15)
  - Germany: Foreign Policy, 1945-1994; Clippings (Box 24 (10-Research materials), Folder 16)
  - Germany: Foreign Policy, 1960-1984; Clippings (Box 25 (10-Research materials), Folder 1)
  - Germany: Law & Judiciary, 1967-1994; Clippings (Box 25 (10-Research materials), Folder 2)
  - Germany: Leftist Movements, 1968-1993; Clippings (Box 25 (10-Research materials), Folder 3)
  - Germany: Legislature, Parliaments, 1965-1994; Clippings (Box 25 (10-Research materials), Folder 4)
  - Germany: Military, 1967-1994; Clippings (Box 25 (10-Research materials), Folder 5)
  - Germany: Nazi criminality, Nazi trials, 1963-1968; Clippings (Box 25 (10-Research materials), Folder 6)
  - Germany: Nazi criminality, Nazi trials, 1969-1977; Clippings (Box 25 (10-Research materials), Folder 7)
  - Germany: Neo-Nazism, Rightist Extremism, 1952-1994; Clippings (Box 25 (10-Research materials), Folder 8)
  - Germany: Ostpolitik, 1967-1974; Clippings, newsletters (Box 25 (10-Research materials), Folder 9)
  - Germany: Political parties, 1967-1994; Clippings (Box 25 (10-Research materials), Folder 10)
  - Germany: Restitution, Indemnification, Rehabilitation, 1939-1994; Clippings (Box 25 (10-Research materials), Folder 11)
  - Germany: Reviews of books on Germany, 1962-1978; Clippings (Box 25 (10-Research materials), Folder 12)
  - Germany: Reunification, 1945-1988; Clippings (Box 25 (10-Research materials), Folder 13)
  - Germany: Reunification, 1989-1993; Clippings (Box 26 (10-Research materials), Folder 1)
  - Germany: Society, Churches, etc, 1970-1994; Clippings (Box 26 (10-Research materials), Folder 2)
  - Germany: Under Nazi Regime, 1944-1994; Clippings (Box 26 (10-Research materials), Folder 3)
  - Germany: War Crimes (including trials), Holocaust, 1951-1994; Clippings (Box 26 (10-Research materials), Folder 4)
  - Germany: West Berlin (until 1990), 1971-1994; Clippings (Box 26 (10-Research materials), Folder 5)
  - Great Britain, 1945-1994; Clippings (Box 26 (10-Research materials), Folder 6)
  - Great Britain: British Empire, Commonwealth, 1945-1992; Clippings (Box 26 (10-Research materials), Folder 7)
  - Great Britain: Foreign Relations, 1939-1991; Clippings (Box 26 (10-Research materials), Folder 8)
  - Greece, 1948-1993; Clippings (Box 26 (10-Research materials), Folder 9)
  - Human Rights Issues, 1947-1994; Clippings (Box 26 (10-Research materials), Folder 10)
  - Hungary, 1947-1994; Clippings (Box 26 (10-Research materials), Folder 11)
  - India, Pakistan, Bangladesh, Thailand, Sri-Lanka, 1955-1994; Clippings (Box 26 (10-Research materials), Folder 12)
  - International Communications & Transportation, 1944-1992; Clippings (Box 26 (10-Research materials), Folder 13)
  - International Courts, International Jurisdiction, 1946-1994; Clippings (Box 26 (10-Research materials), Folder 14)
  - International Courts: Cases, 1948-1994; Clippings (Box 26 (10-Research materials), Folder 15)
  - International Labor Problems, 1945-1994; Clippings (Box 26 (10-Research materials), Folder 16)
  - International Law, 1974-1977; Clippings (Box 26 (10-Research materials), Folder 17)
  - International Law: Extracts from books & articles, Undated (Box 26 (10-Research materials), Folder 18)
  - International Law & Municipal (domestic) Law, 1949-1991; Clippings (Box 26 (10-Research materials), Folder 19)
  - International Law & Relations, Theories, 1948-1992; Clippings (Box 26 (10-Research materials), Folder 20)
  - International Law: Acquisition of territory, 1939-1991; Clippings (Box 27 (10-Research materials), Folder 1)
  - International Law: Aggression, definition of, 1941-1974; Clippings (Box 27 (10-Research materials), Folder 2)
  - International Law: Air & Space Law, 1958-1992; Clippings (Box 27 (10-Research materials), Folder 3)
  - International Law: Asylum, Extradition, 1944-1994; Clippings (Box 27 (10-Research materials), Folder 4)
  - International Law: Blockades & other methods short of war, 1946-1993; Clippings (Box 27 (10-Research materials), Folder 5)
  - International Law: Boundaries, 1939-1992; Clippings (Box 27 (10-Research materials), Folder 6)
  - International Law: Citizenship, 1949-1992; Clippings (Box 27 (10-Research materials), Folder 7)
  - International Law: Diplomatic Representation (Diplomats, Embassies, Consulates), 1946-1994; Clippings (Box 27 (10-Research materials), Folder 8)
  - International Law: Extraterritoriality, 1941-1960; Clippings (Box 27 (10-Research materials), Folder 9)
  - International Law: High Seas, 1945-1994; Clippings (Box 27 (10-Research materials), Folder 10)
  - International Law: International Areas, Protectorates, Dominions, 1940-1987; Clippings (Box 27 (10-Research materials), Folder 11)
  - International Law: Land Warfare, 1952-1993; Clippings (Box 27 (10-Research materials), Folder 12)
  - International Law: Law of Aerial Warfare, 1941-1985; Clippings (Box 27 (10-Research materials), Folder 13)
  - International Law: Law of Maritime Warfare, 1941-1987; Clippings (Box 27 (10-Research materials), Folder 14)
  - International Law: Law of Military Occupation, 1943-1991; Clippings (Box 27 (10-Research materials), Folder 15)